Miss Tsuda!
Thanks to your help the other day,
the project didn't wind up falling through.
I'm really sorry for having
troubled you with all of this!
Miss Ito,
we're on the same team.
Of course I'm going to back you up!
And besides, whatever the case...
I'm plenty happy with a simple "thank you."
- Tsuda!
- Coming!
Thank you so much! Thank you! Thank—
I want to go over the details for
tomorrow's presentation. You mind?
Sure, I'm fine with that.
So, as for features we can
add to the language area...
I work for a major
electronics manufacturer,
in the planning department for
Al-equipped home-use robots,
which keeps me busy on the daily.
All right, that's it for me for today!
What's so great about virtual reality?
Sure, the section lead said that
AI wasn't going to take my job!
But he can't know that for sure!
What if I do lose my job to the hot
new Al and wind up unemployed?!
I might die of loneliness
in this filthy pit...
I'll hire myself a pretty little maid!
All-purpose maid robot? Nope!
Maid cafe? Nope!
Wow, they left something
this big unattended?
Oof, this is heavy!
Wait, better open the
door first! Oh, darn it!
Master?
Master, please wake up.
Good morning, master!
Did you sleep well last night?
Who are you?
Where'd you come from?!
From the cardboard box at the front door.
That enormous box...!
Did I buy an actual human girl?!
Not at all!
Look. I have a socket
here on the back of my neck.
I am a gynoid developed for romance.
My name is Nadeshiko!
That sounds shady!
This has to be illegal!
I'm gonna get arrested... and charged..
- and fired...
- Now, now.
First, just touch me as I go over
my usage functions.
They're so soft...
I was constructed with an
"idealized human form" body concept,
and I am outfitted with
finely tuned pressure sensors
that can respond to even the
most subtle of stimula— mmph!
Can you feel that?
Yes...
Not even my company has
humanoid robots this elaborate...
Master....
Where did that come from?!
You were staring at my lips,
so I thought you wanted a kiss.
Yeah but I was just thinking it!
Did it not feel good?
I am certain that my oral
cavity's specs are fine, so...
How about my genitalia?
That's... downright incredible.
If you would insert your finger,
I can officially register you as my master.
I... I'm not sure about that...
I see. Then you're a bottom, master.
Don't take everything I say as horny!
Understood.
Then we will conduct master
registration at another time.
Lastly, we'll perform a direct
demonstration of my body.
Now, relax, and leave everything to me...
- Wait! Where are you putting that finger?!
- Do not worry.
I assure you I'll guide you to ecstasy.
I have multiple sensors
in my tongue and fingertips
capable of detecting areas of sensitivity.
Ah, here we go.
Also, I am compiling a detailed
report on our sexual activity,
so that the quality of our sexual experience
will improve as we do more things.
So does that mean...
this girl is going to have a record
of all my most embarrassing spots?!
I just activated my finger's vibe function.
By smoothly modulating the strength and direction of the vibration,
I've... never done this before...
in order to increase pleasure...
but it feels so good!
I can't stop! Oh, no...
Brought to you by [ToonsHub]
It's a good thing you
had the day off from work.
Thanks to that,
I was able to tend to
you all day long, master!
I think my life might be over...